<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Dance Classes</string>
    <string name="dance_classes">Dance Classes</string>

    <string-array name="titles_array">
        <item> Ballet Beginner </item>
        <item> Ballet Intermediate </item>
        <item> Ballet Conditioning All-Levels </item>
        <item> Jazz Beginner-Intermediate </item>
        <item> Tap Intermediate </item>
        <item> Salsa Beginner </item>
        <item> Salsa Intermediate </item>
        <item> Contemporary Intermediate </item>
        <item> Contemporary Advanced </item>
        <item> Hip Hop All Levels </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="descs_array">
        <item> The beginner ballet class runs Mondays 5pm - 6pm. </item>
        <item> The intermediate ballet class runs Mondays 6pm - 7pm. </item>
        <item> The ballet conditioning class runs Saturdays 10am-11am. </item>
        <item> The beginner-intermediate jazz class runs Mondays 7pm-9pm. </item>
        <item> The intermediate tap class runs Wednesdays 6pm-7pm. </item>
        <item> All salsa classes will start running in November 2020, day and time TBD. </item>
        <item> All salsa classes will start running in November 2020, day and time TBD. </item>
        <item> The intermediate contemporary class runs Tuesdays 6pm-7pm. </item>
        <item> The advanced contemporary class runs Tuesdays 7pm-8pm. </item>
        <item> The hip hop class runs Thursdays 6pm-7pm and Fridays 5pm-6pm. </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="longdescs_array">
        <item> This is a placeholder for the long description text for the beginner ballet class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the beginner ballet class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the beginner ballet class! \n \nThis is a placeholder for the long description text for the beginner ballet class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the beginner ballet class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the beginner ballet class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the beginner ballet class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the beginner ballet class! </item>
        <item> This is a placeholder for the long description text for the intermediate ballet class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the intermediate ballet class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the intermediate ballet class!\n\nThis is a placeholder for the long description text for the intermediate ballet class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the intermediate ballet class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the intermediate ballet class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the intermediate ballet class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the intermediate ballet class!  </item>
        <item> This is a placeholder for the long description text for the ballet conditioning class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the ballet conditioning class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the ballet conditioning class!\n\n This is a placeholder for the long description text for the ballet conditioning class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the ballet conditioning class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the ballet conditioning class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the ballet conditioning class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the ballet conditioning class! </item>
        <item> This is a placeholder for the long description text for the jazz class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the jazz class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the jazz class!\n\n This is a placeholder for the long description text for the jazz class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the jazz class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the jazz class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the jazz class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the jazz class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the jazz class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the jazz class! </item>
        <item> This is a placeholder for the long description text for the tap class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the tap class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the tap class!\n\n This is a placeholder for the long description text for the tap class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the tap class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the tap class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the tap class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the tap class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the tap class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the tap class! </item>
        <item> This is a placeholder for the long description text for the beginner salsa class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the beginner salsa class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the beginner salsa class!\n\n This is a placeholder for the long description text for the beginner salsa class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the beginner salsa class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the beginner salsa class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the beginner salsa class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the beginner salsa class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the beginner salsa class! </item>
        <item> This is a placeholder for the long description text for the intermediate salsa class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the intermediate salsa class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the intermediate salsa class!\n\n This is a placeholder for the long description text for the intermediate salsa class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the intermediate salsa class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the intermediate salsa class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the intermediate salsa class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the intermediate salsa class! </item>
        <item> This is a placeholder for the long description text for the intermediate contemporary class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the intermediate contemporary class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the intermediate contemporary class!\n\n This is a placeholder for the long description text for the intermediate contemporary class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the intermediate contemporary class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the intermediate contemporary class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the intermediate contemporary class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the intermediate contemporary class! </item>
        <item> This is a placeholder for the long description text for the advanced contemporary class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the advanced contemporary class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the advanced contemporary class!\n\n This is a placeholder for the long description text for the advanced contemporary class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the advanced contemporary class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the advanced contemporary class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the advanced contemporary class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the advanced contemporary class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the advanced contemporary class! </item>
        <item> This is a placeholder for the long description text for the hip hop class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the hip hop class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the hip hop class!\n\n This is a placeholder for the long description text for the hip hop class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the hip hop class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the hip hop class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the hip hop class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the hip hop class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the hip hop class! This is a placeholder for the long description text for the hip hop class! </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>